{"data":[{"question":"He has less friends in his classes now than he had last year.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"less","b":"his","c":"than","d":"last year","answer":"1","explain":" less -> fewer","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The town we visited was a four-days journey from our hotel, so we took the train instead of the bus.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"four-days","c":"took","d":"of the","answer":"2","explain":" - Four-days-> four-day","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The influence of the nation's literature, art, and science have captured widespread  attention.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"nation's","b":"science","c":"have","d":"widespread","answer":"3","explain":" - Have-> has","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The leader emphasized the need for justice and equality between his people.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the need","b":"for justice","c":"between","d":"people","answer":"3","explain":" - Between-> among","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Many of the population in the rural areas is composed of manual laborers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Many","b":"rural areas","c":"composed of","d":"laborers","answer":"1","explain":" - Many-> most ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Several people have apparent tried to change the man's mind, but he refuses to listen.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"apparent","c":"the man's mind","d":"to listen","answer":"2","explain":"  - Apparent-> apparently","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Keith is one of the most intelligent boys of the science class.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the","b":"most","c":"of","d":"science","answer":"3","explain":" - Of-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The girls were sorry to had missed the singers when they arrived at the airport.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were sorry","b":"had missed","c":"when","d":"arrived at","answer":"2","explain":" - Had missed-> miss","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"When Keith visited Alaska, he lived in a igloo in the winter months as well as in the spring.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"lived","b":"a","c":"months","d":"as well as","answer":"2","explain":" - A-> an","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The harder he tried, the worst he danced before the large audience.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"tried","b":"worst","c":"danced","d":"large","answer":"2","explain":" - Worst-> worse","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}